http://www.geosyntec.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Last updated: October 16, 2019
This privacy policy is intended to serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personal Information' (Personal Information) is being used online. As required by state law and also as described in the Data Protection Act 2018 (2018 Act) and the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Personal Information is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information.
If you are a visitor to our webpages
What Personal Information do we collect from the people that visit our website?
When completing a form on our site you may be asked to enter your first and last name, personal or business email address phone number and/or mailing address, and other details to help us communicate with you.
When you visit our website, our web server uses your Internet Protocol address (IP address) to communicate with you. An IP address is like a phone number because it is a numerical label assigned to each device connected to the internet that uses the Internet Protocol for communication. An IP address allows the server to send information to your computer as web pages by knowing where your computer is located.
When do we collect Personal Information?
We collect your Personal Information when you fill out any on-line form, opt-in to receive email, or just visit our site.
What is our lawful basis for processing your Personal Information?
We rely on the Legitimate Interest basis under the GDPR. We need your Personal Information to help us identify services you inquire about or ask us to perform or to send you newsletters, surveys, and other information advertising our services. You need to provide your Personal Information, so we can communicate with you or to help you to determine the suitability of our services to address your needs.
How do we use your Personal Information?
We may use your Personal Information to send you information advertising our services, or when you sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
Improve our website to better serve you
To send periodic emails regarding services you expressed interest in
To follow up with you after correspondence
Protect our website from malicious use
You have the right to object to our use of your Personal Information for newsletters, surveys, or marketing and can ask us to stop using your Personal Information at any time by informing us at any of the contacts below.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are also used to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's help information to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, it won't affect your experience on our site.
Do we disclose your Personal Information to third-parties?
Yes. We use a trusted third-party service called Google Analytics as a data processor to track user information
on our behalf. You can find detailed information on how they safeguard your data on their website.
We also use the trusted email marketing service providers Constant Contact and MailChimp to collect email addresses and manage our email marketing. The privacy policy for Mailchimp and the privacy policy for Constant Contact can be found on their respective websites.
How do we process/obtain opt-in/opt-out notices for marketing purposes?
When you sign up to receive marketing emails from us (opt-in), your information is added to the email provider's secure database for use by us. Every email you receive will contain a link to unsubscribe (opt-out) at the bottom of the email.
Who can you contact to address your requests for access to your Personal Information or your requests to object to our further processing of your Personal Information?
We are not required to appoint a Data Protection Officer (DPO) as outlined in the GDPR. However, if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to use your right to request removal of your Personal Information from our systems, please complete the online removal request form by clicking here. You may also contact us directly using the information provided below.
Phone: +1-866-676-1101 (toll free in the United States)
Postal Mail:
Geosyntec Consultants
ATTN: Privacy Policy Questions – Human Resources
900 Broken Sound Parkway NW, Suite 200
Boca Raton, Florida 33487
USA
+1-866-676-1101
Contact Us »
Geosyntec is a consulting and engineering firm that works with private and public sector clients to address new ventures and complex problems involving our environment, natural resources, and civil infrastructure.
Connect with us
LinkedIn
facebook
twitter
instagram
Our Businesses
SiREM Lab »
Savron »
Geosyntec Europe »
login
Markets
All Market Sectors
Aerospace and Electronics
Agribusiness
Chemicals and Petrochemicals
Dams
Electric Power Utilities
Water and Natural Resources
Geotechnical and Geological Analysis, Modeling, and Engineering
Air Quality Management and Air Pollution Control
People
Browse People
Filter People
Publications & Presentations
Filter Publications & Presentations
Academic & Research Contributions
Projects
Main Menu
MarketsAll Market SectorsAerospace and ElectronicsAgribusinessChemicals and PetrochemicalsDamsServices for DamsDam Structural ServicesDam Risk Evaluation and MitigationDam Hydrology, Hydraulics, and Water QualityDam InspectionDam Geotechnical ServicesDam Hydropower Licensing and ComplianceDam Construction Information Management SystemsDam Geotechnical Instrumentation and Monitoring ServicesElectric Power UtilitiesCoal Combustion Residuals and ByproductsAir Quality ServicesElectric TransmissionServices for Electric Power UtilitiesWater and Wastewater ServicesGovernmentServices for GovernmentsFederal Departments and AgenciesState Departments and AgenciesMunicipalities, Counties, and LocalIndustrial Water SolutionsServices for Industrial WaterRefinery Water and Wastewater Treatment and ManagementLegal CounselManufacturingMiningServices for MinesMines: Infrastructure Planning and PermittingMines: Geotechnical Engineering of Earthen Structures and ImpoundmentsMines: Water Management, Treatment, Reuse, and RecyclingMines: Litigation Support and Environmental Liability ValuationMines: EHS Compliance and ManagementMines: Site Closure, Reclamation, and ConversionOil and GasPharmaceuticals and BiotechnologyOverview of Pharmaceuticals and BiotechnologyPharmaceuticals in the EnvironmentEHS Services for Pharmaceutical, Biotechnology, Related Chemical OperationsReal Estate, Insurance and FinanceResilience and AdaptationSolid Waste Engineering and AdvisorySolid Waste EngineeringSolid Waste Advisory ServicesPracticesCOVID-19 ServicesContaminated Site Assessment and CleanupOverview of Contaminated Site Assessment and CleanupVapor Intrusion Assessment and RemediationSediment Assessment and RemediationPer- and Polyfluoroalkyl Substances (PFAS)Conceptual Site Model DevelopmentContaminated Media Investigations and AssessmentsGroundwater Assessment and RemediationAir Quality Management and Air Pollution ControlWaste Management Planning, Engineering, and DesignEnvironmental Forensic StudiesFate and Transport Studies and ModelingFeasibility Studies and Remediation System DesignHuman Health and Ecological Risk AssessmentsHydrogeological Characterization and ModelingDetection and Culturing of Microbes for Environmental ApplicationsRegulatory Strategy and Cleanup Goal DevelopmentRemediation System Operation and OptimizationTreatability and Pilot StudiesEnvironmental Data ClearinghouseCivil Site Engineering and DesignOverview of Civil Site Engineering and DesignBrownfield Redevelopment Planning and DesignConstructed Wetland Treatment SystemsFacility Decontamination and DecommissioningIndustrial Wastewater Treatment SystemsLandfill Gas Collection and Management SystemsLandfill Gas to Energy SystemsRadiological Waste Management and Disposal FacilitiesSolid Waste Recycling FacilitiesSolid, Industrial, and Hazardous Waste Disposal FacilitiesSpring Water Supply SystemsData Interpretation, Synthesis, Visualization, and GISWater Supply Production WellsEnvironmental Planning and ManagementOverview of Environmental Planning and ManagementManagement Systems ServicesEnvironmental Permitting and CompliancePollution Prevention ServicesWaste Management and Minimization ServicesOperational Risk ManagementProcess Safety Management and Risk Management Program Compliance Occupational Safety and HealthBuilding Health Evaluations and RehabilitationTransactional Due Diligence and ConsultationOverview of Transactional Due Diligence and ConsultationEnvironmental Liability ValuationsCapital, Assets, and Transaction Advisory (CAT)Water and Natural ResourcesOverview of Water and Natural ResourcesDischarge Permitting and Receiving Water StudiesSpring Water Source StudiesHydropower Licensing and ComplianceIntegrated Water Resource Management PlanningLow Impact Development, Green Infrastructure, Sustainable PracticesNatural Resource Damage AssessmentsNatural Resource MonitoringReservoir and Lake Thermal Studies and ModelingStream and Lake Restoration Studies and DesignUrban Stormwater Management Planning and DesignWatershed and Water Quality Studies and ModelingResilience and AdaptationGeotechnical and Geological Analysis, Modeling, and EngineeringOverview of Geotechnical and Geological Analysis, Modeling, and EngineeringEarth Retaining Structures and Excavation SupportEarthquake EngineeringGeohazard Evaluation and MitigationGeotechnical and Geostructural EngineeringLevees, Dams, and Subsurface Hydraulic BarriersSeismic Hazard Evaluation and Ground Motion StudiesSoft and Liquefiable Ground ImprovementSoil and Structure Interaction StudiesSpecialty and Conventional Structural FoundationsGeostructural and Construction EngineeringAir Quality Management and Air Pollution ControlOverview of Air Quality Management and Air Pollution ControlEnergy Transition and Carbon ReductionClimate Change and Greenhouse Gas EvaluationsAir Dispersion ModelingAir Pollution Control Evaluations and Performance AssessmentsAir Quality Permitting and ComplianceHazardous Air Pollutant Control Program Development and ImplementationContinuous Emission Monitoring System Design and ImplementationToxic Air Contaminants and Risk AssessmentsAir Quality Litigation SupportEnvironmental, Social, and GovernanceList of All PracticesPeopleOur PeoplePublications & PresentationsAcademic & Research ContributionsProjectsAboutDiversity and InclusionAbout GeosyntecLocationsContact UsMission and ValuesSustainabilitySupplier DiversityHealth and SafetySpecialty ServicesCareersView Global Career OpportunitiesCareers at GeosyntecA Great Place to WorkProfessional Development and GrowthEmployee BenefitsContributions to the CommunityThe Geosyntec Career ExperienceEEO and Affirmative ActionNewsSearch
